(Leonard:)That was a big milestone for me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, speaking of personal growth,
(Sheldon:)I recently tried eating
Swiss chard.
(Sheldon:)You know, I didn't swallow it,
but Amy said it counted.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
Hey.
(Stuart:)Still a loser or
did you turn things around
(Stuart:)while you were gone?
(Penny:)You know, Raj, honey,
(Penny:)you're being
too hard on yourself.
(Penny:)When I first met you,
you couldn't even talk to women.
(Penny:)I mean, you couldn't even talk
if one was in the room.
(Raj:)Oh, great, now I can say
things like “I can't believe
you're breaking up with me.”
“Why are you breaking up
with me?”
“Yes, I'll still help you move”"
(Penny:)Anyone else want to try?
(Stuart:)Uh, yeah, I got something.
(Bernadette:)Raj,
(Stuart:)not everybody
could be a dog owner.
(Stuart:)Oh, what? Did your doggie
break up with you too?
(Penny:)Hey, I bought M&Ms
at the vending machine